<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<dataroot xmlns:od="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:officedata" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"  xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="people.xsd" generated="2011-11-05T23:09:59">
    <player>
        <name>David De Gea</name>
        <nationality>Spain</nationality>
        <age>31</age>
        <position>Goalkeeper</position>
        <shirtNum>1</shirtNum>
        <image>degea</image>
        <appearances>504</appearances>
        <goals>0</goals>
        <assists>0</assists>
        <majorTrophies>6</majorTrophies>
        <bio>David de Gea Quintana (born 7 November 1990) is the current first choice goalkeeper for Manchester United. During the mid-2010s, he was widely regarded as one of the best goalkeepers in the world.</bio>
        <quote>I don’t know who is the best goalkeeper in the world at the moment, but I want to be the best.</quote>
    </player>
    <player>
        <name>Tom Heaton</name>
        <nationality>England</nationality>
        <age>36</age>
        <position>Goalkeeper</position>
        <shirtNum>22</shirtNum>
        <image>heaton</image>
        <appearances>1</appearances>
        <goals>0</goals>
        <assists>0</assists>
        <majorTrophies>0</majorTrophies>
        <bio>Tom Heaton (born 15 November 1986) is a veteran goalkeeper who recently resigned for his boyhood club, Manchester United. </bio>
        <quote>I still feel I’ve got an awful lot to give and I’ve got the bit between my teeth.</quote>
    </player>
    <player>
        <name>Martin Dubravka</name>
        <nationality>Slovakia</nationality>
        <age>33</age>
        <position>Goalkeeper</position>
        <shirtNum>31</shirtNum>
        <image>dubravka</image>
        <appearances>0</appearances>
        <goals>0</goals>
        <assists>0</assists>
        <majorTrophies>0</majorTrophies>
        <bio>Martin Dubravka (born 15 January 1989) who has recently joined Manchester United on loan from Newcastle after a number of impressive seasons at the Tyne Side club.</bio>
        <quote>My ambition is to play. It's part of why I came here, I feel I can be part of a great club, a great dressing room.</quote>
    </player>
    <player>
        <name>Victor Lindelof</name>
        <nationality>Sweeden</nationality>
        <age>28</age>
        <position>Defender</position>
        <shirtNum>2</shirtNum>
        <image>lindelof</image>
        <appearances>203</appearances>
        <goals>3</goals>
        <assists>5</assists>
        <majorTrophies>0</majorTrophies>
        <bio>Victor Lindelof (born 17 July 1994) has been a first-team regular at Manchester United since he signed from Benfica in 2017 as well as captaining the Sweedish national team on numerous occasions. Victor is mainly deployed at centre back however can also fill in on the right side of defence.</bio>
        <quote>United are one of the biggest clubs in the world and always want to win titles. That’s also my goal.</quote>
    </player>
    <player>
        <name>Phil Jones</name>
        <nationality>England</nationality>
        <age>30</age>
        <position>Defender</position>
        <shirtNum>4</shirtNum>
        <image>jones</image>
        <appearances>229</appearances>
        <goals>6</goals>
        <assists>7</assists>
        <majorTrophies>4</majorTrophies>
        <bio>Phil Jones (born 21 February 1992) has played for Manchester United since he signed from Blackburn in 2011. Initially showing a lot of promise, Jones has been unfortunately plagued by injuries throughout his career and not quite hit the hights he had hoped to. In spite of this he has made over 200 appearances for the club and has been a valuable asset to the team for over 10 years.</bio>
        <quote>I just love to defend. I want to stop goals going in the net.</quote>
    </player>
    <player>
        <name>Harry Maguire</name>
        <nationality>England</nationality>
        <age>29</age>
        <position>Defender</position>
        <shirtNum>5</shirtNum>
        <image>maguire</image>
        <appearances>151</appearances>
        <goals>7</goals>
        <assists>2</assists>
        <majorTrophies>0</majorTrophies>
        <bio>Harry Maguire (born 5 March 1993) is the current captain of the football club. Signing from Leicester for 80 million pounds in the summer of 2019 Maguire had been a valuable member at the heart of the defence before falling out of favour this season in favour of new signing Lisandro Martinez.</bio>
        <quote>It's an amazing club. It's a club I've always watched and I always looked up to when I was younger.</quote>
    </player>
    <player>
        <name>Raphael Varane</name>
        <nationality>France</nationality>
        <age>29</age>
        <position>Defender</position>
        <shirtNum>19</shirtNum>
        <image>varane</image>
        <appearances>40</appearances>
        <goals>1</goals>
        <assists>1</assists>
        <majorTrophies>20</majorTrophies>
        <bio>Raphael Varane (born 25 April 1993) is one of the greatest defenders of the generation. Having won the lot at Real Madrid including 3 Champion Leagues in a row along with the World Cup with France, Varane joined the club in 2021 and plays at the heart of the defence next to Lisandro Martinez.</bio>
        <quote>I came here because I wanted new emotions and it was exactly what I expected and bigger.</quote>
    </player>
    <player>
        <name>Diogo Dalot</name>
        <nationality>Portugal</nationality>
        <age>23</age>
        <position>Defender</position>
        <shirtNum>20</shirtNum>
        <image>dalot</image>
        <appearances>82</appearances>
        <goals>2</goals>
        <assists>1</assists>
        <majorTrophies>1</majorTrophies>
        <bio>Diogo Dalot (born 18 March 1999) was signed by Jose Mourinho and was said to be an investment for years to come. That investment is beginning to pay off as he has found a place in the first eleven with a string of great performances this season.</bio>
        <quote>I will give everything for this club, for this shirt and, hopefully, help the club to win. That’s the most important thing.</quote>
    </player>
    <player>
        <name>Luke Shaw</name>
        <nationality>England</nationality>
        <age>27</age>
        <position>Defender</position>
        <shirtNum>23</shirtNum>
        <image>shaw</image>
        <appearances>255</appearances>
        <goals>3</goals>
        <assists>20</assists>
        <majorTrophies>3</majorTrophies>
        <bio>luke Shaw (born12 July 1995) signed from Southampton in 2014. After a horrible leg break in his first season, Shaw struggled for consistency and found himself in and out of the team. However, for periods of time Shaw has shown his quality and is currently a regular starter with hopes of representing England at the upcoming World Cup.</bio>
        <quote>I’ve got the freedom to play and that gives me the confidence in what I want to do to help the team.</quote>
    </player>
    <player>
        <name>Aaron Wan-Bissaka</name>
        <nationality>England</nationality>
        <age>24</age>
        <position>Defender</position>
        <shirtNum>29</shirtNum>
        <image>wanbissaka</image>
        <appearances>127</appearances>
        <goals>2</goals>
        <assists>9</assists>
        <majorTrophies>0</majorTrophies>
        <bio>Arron Wan-Bissaka (born 26 November 1997) signed from Crystal Palace in 2019. Being a master of the slide tackle there are not manny better players out there at 1v1 defending. However other aspects of his game have room for improvement esoecially if he wants to find himself back in the starting eleven over Diogo Dalot.</bio>
        <quote>Every kid wants to play for a team like this. It's an honour to represent this club.</quote>
    </player>
    <player>
        <name>Tyrell Malacia</name>
        <nationality>Netherlands</nationality>
        <age>23</age>
        <position>Defender</position>
        <shirtNum>12</shirtNum>
        <image>malacia</image>
        <appearances>12</appearances>
        <goals>0</goals>
        <assists>0</assists>
        <majorTrophies>0</majorTrophies>
        <bio>Tyrell Malacia (born 17 August 1999) is a young Dutch left back who recently signed from the club from Feyenoord. Showing lots of promise in his first string of games of the clubs there are high hopes for this bright young player's future.</bio>
        <quote>Whilst I know that I am still young and will continue to develop, I can promise the United fans that I will leave everything on the pitch.</quote>
    </player>
    <player>
        <name>Lisandro Martinez</name>
        <nationality>Argentina</nationality>
        <age>24</age>
        <position>Defender</position>
        <shirtNum>6</shirtNum>
        <image>martinez</image>
        <appearances>17</appearances>
        <goals>0</goals>
        <assists>0</assists>
        <majorTrophies>5</majorTrophies>
        <bio>Lisandro Martinez (born 18 January 1988) recently followed manager Erik Ten Haag over from Ajax to join Manchester United. There were a lot of doubts around this signing due to his short stature but he has been quick to silence the critics with multiple man of the match, inspirational performances at the heart of the defence.</bio>
        <quote>I’ve worked so hard to get to this moment and, now that I’m here, I’m going to push myself even further.</quote>
    </player>
    <player>
        <name>Fred</name>
        <nationality>Brazil</nationality>
        <age>29</age>
        <position>Midfielder</position>
        <shirtNum>17</shirtNum>
        <image>fred</image>
        <appearances>171</appearances>
        <goals>9</goals>
        <assists>12</assists>
        <majorTrophies>0</majorTrophies>
        <bio>Fred (born 5 March 1993) is a Brazilian midfielder who joined the club in 2018. Featuring both as a 6 and as an 8 at times Fred has been a main stay of the first team since he signed. Fred is an exciting player who can be a threat going forward however despite his efforts sometimes a liability defensively. Overall a great asset to the squad.</bio>
        <quote>I will never forget how I felt the day I made my debut at Old Trafford. It was just fantastic.</quote>
    </player>
    <player>
        <name>Bruno Fernandes</name>
        <nationality>Portugal</nationality>
        <age>28</age>
        <position>Midfielder</position>
        <shirtNum>8</shirtNum>
        <image>bruno</image>
        <appearances>143</appearances>
        <goals>52</goals>
        <assists>38</assists>
        <majorTrophies>1</majorTrophies>
        <bio>Bruno Fernandes (born 8 September 1994) is one of the best creative midfielders in the world. Since singing from Sporting in January 2020 Bruno has been a fan favourite with his outrageous chance creation and goal contributions. Bruno is a leader on the pitch and one of United's best players.</bio>
        <quote>To play for United feels incredible. I can promise the fans I will give everything to help bring us success.</quote>
    </player>
    <player>
        <name>Scott McTominay</name>
        <nationality>Scotland</nationality>
        <age>25</age>
        <position>Midfielder</position>
        <shirtNum>39</shirtNum>
        <image>mctominay</image>
        <appearances>185</appearances>
        <goals>17</goals>
        <assists>4</assists>
        <majorTrophies>0</majorTrophies>
        <bio>Scott McTominay (born 8 December 1996) is a product of the famous Man United youth academy. The industrious midfielder has been an asset to the team since making his debut in 2017 featuring as a defensive midfielder, popping up with the occasional goal.</bio>
        <quote>You've got to keep working hard. The moment you stop is when things can go bad for you.</quote>
    </player>
    <player>
        <name>Donny Van de Beek</name>
        <nationality>Netherlands</nationality>
        <age>25</age>
        <position>Midfielder</position>
        <shirtNum>34</shirtNum>
        <image>donny</image>
        <appearances>54</appearances>
        <goals>2</goals>
        <assists>1</assists>
        <majorTrophies>2</majorTrophies>
        <bio>Donny Van de Beek (born 18 April 1997) has struggled to break into the first team since he arrived from Ajax in 2020. After a disappointing loan spell at Everton Donny hopes to make a change as he reunites with his former boss from Ajax Erik Ten Haag at the Manchester club.</bio>
        <quote>I am ready to take the next step in my career and there is no higher standard than Manchester United.</quote>
    </player>
    <player>
        <name>Christian Eriksen</name>
        <nationality>Denmark</nationality>
        <age>30</age>
        <position>Midfielder</position>
        <shirtNum>14</shirtNum>
        <image>eriksen</image>
        <appearances>16</appearances>
        <goals>0</goals>
        <assists>5</assists>
        <majorTrophies>5</majorTrophies>
        <bio>Christian Eriksen (born 14 February 1992) has been one of the best creative midfielders the Premier League has seen from the mid 2010's till now. Following his health scare and triumphant return to the Premier League at Brentford Christian joined United with the hopes of bringing glory back to the famous reds.</bio>
        <quote>It feels good to be here. It's very special.</quote>
    </player>
    <player>
        <name>Casemiro</name>
        <nationality>Brazil</nationality>
        <age>30</age>
        <position>Midfielder</position>
        <shirtNum>18</shirtNum>
        <image>casemiro</image>
        <appearances>14</appearances>
        <goals>1</goals>
        <assists>1</assists>
        <majorTrophies>20</majorTrophies>
        <bio>Casemiro (born 23 February 1992) is one of the best defensive midfielders of our generation. After winning his 5th Champions Leagues with Real Madrid, Casemiro opted to join the reds this summer for a new challenge and has quickly become a fan favourite at the club.</bio>
        <quote>To represent United is an honour and I am ready to give everything to help the team achieve our ambitions.</quote>
    </player>
    <player>
        <name>Cristiano Ronaldo</name>
        <nationality>Portugal</nationality>
        <age>37</age>
        <position>Forward</position>
        <shirtNum>7</shirtNum>
        <image>ronaldo</image>
        <appearances>344</appearances>
        <goals>145</goals>
        <assists>56</assists>
        <majorTrophies>30</majorTrophies>
        <bio>Cristiano Ronaldo. Arguably the greatest footballer of all time has returned to Manchester United. After his logic defying spells at Real Madrid and Juventus winning all there is to win, this legend of the game is back at Old Trafford. Having recently scored his 700th career club goal, Ronaldo continues to break records into his late 30's.</bio>
        <quote>History has been written in the past and history will be written once again. You have my word.</quote>
    </player>
    <player>
        <name>Marcus Rashford</name>
        <nationality>England</nationality>
        <age>25</age>
        <position>Forward</position>
        <shirtNum>10</shirtNum>
        <image>rash</image>
        <appearances>318</appearances>
        <goals>100</goals>
        <assists>38</assists>
        <majorTrophies>3</majorTrophies>
        <bio>Marcus Rashford (born 31 October 1997) is a role model both on and off the pitch. His path to the first team from the academy has been inspirational and he has been a major asset since he took his opportunity against FC Mijtdlyand in 2017. Recently breaking 100 goals for the club there is still a lot to come from Marcus.</bio>
        <quote>I have always been a United fan, so to be playing in the first team really is a dream come true.</quote>
    </player>
    <player>
        <name>Antony</name>
        <nationality>Brazil</nationality>
        <age>22</age>
        <position>Forward</position>
        <shirtNum>21</shirtNum>
        <image>antony</image>
        <appearances>11</appearances>
        <goals>3</goals>
        <assists>0</assists>
        <majorTrophies>4</majorTrophies>
        <bio>Antony (born 24 February 2000) is an exciting Brazilian winger recently signed from Ajax. Antony gets the fans off their seats with his tricks and quick dribbles and proves to be a threat down the right side of the United attack.</bio>
        <quote>In Antony, Manchester United have a dynamic winger who can light up the right-hand side of our attack.</quote>
    </player>
    <player>
        <name>Jadon Sancho</name>
        <nationality>England</nationality>
        <age>22</age>
        <position>Forward</position>
        <shirtNum>25</shirtNum>
        <image>sancho</image>
        <appearances>52</appearances>
        <goals>8</goals>
        <assists>4</assists>
        <majorTrophies>2</majorTrophies>
        <bio>Jadon Sancho (born 25 March 2000) is one of the brightest young talents in the world. Although still finding his feet in Manchester, Sancho has undeniable skill and talent and promises to be a great player for the reds in years to come.</bio>
        <quote>Growing up, United was one of the biggest clubs that everyone knows. So I'm very happy to be wearing this jersey now.</quote>
    </player>
    <player>
        <name>Anthony Martial</name>
        <nationality>France</nationality>
        <age>26</age>
        <position>Forward</position>
        <shirtNum>9</shirtNum>
        <image>martial</image>
        <appearances>273</appearances>
        <goals>82</goals>
        <assists>31</assists>
        <majorTrophies>4</majorTrophies>
        <bio>Anthony Martial (born 5 December 1995) has been a solid player in the United squad despite lacking consistency at times. When on form he is a lethal finisher and skillful dribbler, a handful for any defender. However over his time at the club his form has been patchy. Let's hope to see Martial consistently at his best in seasons to come.</bio>
        <quote>I love Manchester United, I love the fans, they give me a lot of joy.</quote>
    </player>
</dataroot>
